Previously on:
So, what happened
between you and your girl?
She wanted to get married, and
I'm just not sure I'm ready.
That's the same reason
I lost Lyndsey.
You got to get her back.
Don't make the same mistake I did.
I am gonna ask Lyndsey
to marry me.
Yeah, I just have to get a ring.
I got a ring you could have.
You must be here
to see your friend Larry,
who is also here.
Lyndsey MacElroy,
will you marry me?
Yes, I will marry you!
(Lyndsey laughing)
What's going on down here?
I got up to pee
and I heard moaning.
No, you heard crying.
(woman moans sensually on TV)
And moaning.
You're watching porn
at 3:00 in the morning?
No, it's that
soft-core flick
that Lyndsey made
back in the '90s,
Cinnamon's Buns.
Nothing brings me back
like hearing her fake an orgasm.
Oh, listen, I know
that breakups are hard, but...
Uh, please tell me
those were for crying.
Oh, yes, yes, uh, yes.
Uh, uh, crying, yes,
very upset, very upset, yes.
Wow, you know, you're
a classy guy, Alan.
It's hard to understand
why she accepted
Larry's proposal and not yours.
Technically, I never
actually proposed.
What?
Well, when I got there
he was already doing it,
so I just figured I'd chalk
this one up as another loss
and move on.
Universe: 82,223;
Alan: 12.
Come on, you're exaggerating.
You have not had 12 victories.
Yes, I have.
Uh, my son, plus the number of years
I've lived here rent-free.
I can't believe
you just stood there
while another guy
proposed to your girl
and you didn't say anything.
There's nothing
I can do about it.
Larry's the one
frosting her muffins now.
Have we learned nothing
from Cinnamon's Buns?
She told Master Baker no
five times!
Did he listen? No!
No, the only reason Lyndsey
settled for Larry
is 'cause she didn't know
she could settle for you!
You're right. I mean,
you're a handsome billionaire,
and you settled for me.
She's just a-a-a divorced,
middle-aged lush...
...of my dreams.
That's the spirit!
Now, get up and...
wash your hands and...
burn this couch,
and go get your...
surprisingly flexible
girlfriend back.
You're right, you're right.
Thanks, Walden.
LYNDSEY (on video):
Oh, Master Baker,
would you like to watch while
I train this lovely young maiden
to churn your butter?
Maybe one more scene.
This is a pivotal
part of the film.
You might need this.
This scene's
a real tear... jerker.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x15 ♪
Cab Fare and a Bottle of Penicillin
Original Air Date on February 27, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, Berta,
how about a cup of coffee?
No, thanks, I just had a cup.
I don't know why
you keep her on payroll.
Says the guy I pay
to be my assistant.
Oh, oh, that's still a thing?
Oh, oh, cup of joe
coming right up, boss.
Hey, what are you
doing there?
I'm making breakfast
in bed for Brooke.
Hey, what tastes good on boobs?
Pineapple rings are always fun.
Yeah. You get the room
nice and cold, and you play ring toss.
Yeah, and with
Brooke's bad boys, you could...
Hey.
Omaha! Omaha!
What? Hmm?
Nothing. We weren't talking
about your boobs.
Why not? You stare
at 'em enough.
(laughs):
What?
(laughing):
I don't... I never...
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
I got to get to work.
You can't leave--
breakfast sex
is the most important meal
of the day.
Sorry. Mwa!
I'll call you later, okay, babe?
No worries.
Call me whenever you can.
Oh, God, she's dumping me.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you just hear that?
She's "going to work."
Okay, I know no one in this
house is familiar with it,
but "going to work"
is an actual thing.
It's kind of like "paying rent".
It's not just that, it's...
it's been forever
since we've had sex.
Well, how long is forever?
Two days!
I hate you.
Come on, you and Brooke
are great together.
She's not breaking up with you.
Uh, then again,
maybe she is slipping away,
and you're just gonna have
to face the possibility
of being alone
for the rest of your life.
(sobbing gasp)
Oh, my God!
(Jenny sobbing)
What the hell's
the matter with you?
Why would you say that to her?
I'm just trying to prepare her
for-for the harsh realities
of real life.
I mean, who else is gonna do it,
her father? He's dead, Walden!
Why are you even here?
I thought you were
gonna go win Lyndsey back.
It's early.
I want to win her back,
but I don't want to spend
the whole day with her.
(doorbell rings)
Alan.
Lyndsey MacElroy, I love you.
You are my world.
I want you to spend
the rest of your life with me.
And Walden.
You're-you're kidding, right?
I'm engaged to Larry.
That's not fair.
I mean, if I hadn't stopped
at that gas station to poop,
I would have been here first.
Alan, don't.
Maybe this will change
your mind.
Oh, Alan, it doesn't matter
what kind of ring...
Holy crap, that thing's huge!
That's what she said.
(chuckles)
I know, not the right time.
What do you say?
I say I'm marrying Larry.
But why?
He loves me.
Not as much as I do.
He has his own house.
I...
love you.
I'm sorry, Alan.
You-you really think Larry can
make you happier than I can?
I think I made
the right decision.
You made your bed.
Now let's have sex in it.
Alan.
Good-bye.
All right.
Universe: 82,224.
Twenty-five.
(sighs)
Alan.
Hi, Judith.
What are you doing here?
Oh, God, what did Jake do?
Please tell me the Army didn't
let him drive a tank again.
No, no, nothing's
wrong with Jake.
Well, nothing new wrong.
Then what's going on?
Is everything okay?
Uh, it's just that I've been
having a really rough day,
and I needed to see
a friendly face.
And you picked me?
There's that friendly face.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you come on in.
I just opened a bottle of wine.
Thanks.
Wait.
You don't need money, do you?
No, not at all.
Okay, good.
Wait, are you offering?
(chuckles):
Whoa, nice blanket.
What's with the cat lady
starter kit?
It's my bad-news blanket.
My mom gave it to me
when I was a kid.
I know what
you're saying.
I have a bad-news bong.
And a good-news bong.
And a watching-the-news bong.
I guess what I'm saying is,
I like to get high.
This about Brooke?
She blew me off again.
She was supposed
to come over after work,
but she said she was tired.
Not having sex with me
must be exhausting.
Look... Jenny,
in any relationship,
it's normal for there to be
a lull in the bedroom
after a while.
Does the sex come back?
(laughs)
You're cute.
But it does help
if you do romantic stuff.
Like what?
Surprise her.
Be spontaneous.
Let her know
that you appreciate her.
I guess I could send flowers
to her work.
Ugh! That's so gay.
Well, these are the kinds
of things we have to do
as a relationship evolves.
See,
sex becomes companionship,
and companionship
becomes commitment.
Commitment...
becomes complacency, which...
gives way to contempt.
Until you find yourself longing
for the sweet release of death.
Yikes.
I'm gonna go get
my bad-news bong.
(clears throat softly)
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Uh, you remember, uh,
Jake's seventh grade
science project?
Wait, which seventh grade?
Second time.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah, yeah.
Um, he wanted to study
how different foods
would make his farts smell.
Oh, yeah! He'd rip one
in Tupperware,
seal it and label it.
Mm.
To this day, I still remember
Brussels sprouts. Yes.
Oh, Brussels sprouts. Ugh...!
Most parents make
their kids eat vegetables.
We made ours stop. Yeah.
Right.
And then he got rickets.
(both cackling)
Oh... oh, it's been
a crazy ride, hasn't it?
Yeah.
Mm.
Hey... can I
ask you something?
Oh, here we go.
How much?
No, no, not that.
What's wrong with me?
Oh, Alan. I don't carry around
a list of your faults.
My therapist said
it's no longer healthy.
I'm-I'm serious.
I mean, it seems like
every relationship I've ever been in
I've screwed up.
Oh. Look, a marriage
doesn't fail
because of one
person screwing up.
I screwed up two marriages.
Oh, yeah,
yeah, you're right--
you're a two-time loser.
Uh, but at least I have Walden;
I mean, you've got nobody.
Oh, we're being
honest now?
Herb's penis is
bigger than yours.
(chuckles) I'd forgotten how good
you are at this.
Ha-ha...
I have missed you.
I mean, you know,
not the constant verbal abuse
that left me
a crippled shell of a man.
But we could always
make each other laugh.
Oh. You could never
find my G-spot,
but you could always
find my funny bone.
(laughing): Aw...
Oh...
I'm just kidding.
I've missed you, too.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm...
Oh, yeah, this is, uh...
This is probably a bad idea.
Definitely.
Yeah, yeah.
(sniffles)
(sighs)
Oh.
(both moaning)
Let's look for that G-spot.
Or... how about
you look for mine?
Mmm. Mmm.
Oh, God.
What did we do?
Mmm.
Oh, God, what did I do?
♪ Men. ♪
(grunts quietly)
Come on.
(sighs)
God.
(whispering):
What did we do last night?
More!
Oh, God.
(sighs)
Oh. Oh.
(mutters)
(panting)
(ringtone plays)
Well, well, well, someone never
made it home last night.
Am I speaking
with an engaged man?
I think you might be.
(laughs)
That's great.
Hey, what'd Lyndsey say
when you showed her the ring?
That thing is huge.
That's what she said.
That's what I said!
She also said
she's staying with Larry.
What? I thought
you said you were engaged.
I am. To Judith.
What, your ex-wife?
Whoa. What the hell happened?
Well, it's all kind of sketchy.
We had a lot to drink.
Well, I-I've had
a lot to drink before,
but I've never got engaged
to my ex-wife.
Okay, maybe I'm being selfish,
but I'd like
to talk about me right now.
Jindsey?
Hmm?
Ludith.
Will you Larry me?
Let me ask you something.
Um, do you think
Judith would be more upset,
uh, to wake up
and find she's engaged to me,
or to wake up
and find she's missing a finger?
Okay, look, I'm sure
that she got tipsy
and caught up
in the moment, too,
and if you're just
honest with her,
she'll probably be relieved.
What if she isn't?
I mean, how do I get her
to want out of marrying me?
Be yourself?
Worked before.
(sighs)
Hey, you.
Um, uh, listen, uh, we should...
we should really talk
about last night.
Absolutely, but I need
to say something first.
Things are going
to be different this time.
I'm not going to make
the same mistakes I made before.
And I'm going to start
by showing you
how much I appreciate you
every single day.
Oh, that's really sweet, but
we really should talk about...
♪ Who we should invite
to the wedding! ♪
Hey.
Hi.
Guess what.
I'm taking your advice,
and I'm surprising Brooke
with a romantic evening.
Good. You know, I know
that's not easy for you.
Your dad was the same way.
His idea of romance
was a warm washcloth,
cab fare
and a bottle of penicillin.
Aw! So my dad wasn't just
a drunken, diseased man-whore.
He was a gentleman.
Charlie would be so happy
to see his little girl now.
Of course,
he'd be even more happy
to see the rack
on his little girl's girlfriend.
Does she have nice boobs?
I've never noticed.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
How'd it go with Judith?
She take it okay?
Uh, well, uh, you know,
she... uh, she...
It was a... a little hard
for her to swallow.
Um...
Well, I'm just glad
you talked to her.
Can I get my ring back?
Uh, funny story.
Um... she kind of kept it,
and we're kind of
getting married.
Alan, I thought
you were gonna talk to her.
Uh, I did.
Uh, we came to an...
oral agreement.
Oh!
Alan!
It's my weakness.
That and red velvet anything.
Wait. Wait.
This is the same woman
that you said was so evil
that her image didn't show up
in your wedding pictures.
I only said that because,
at the time,
I thought she was
the worst person I'd ever met,
and she made my life
a living hell.
But, you know, people change.
It's gonna be great.
So, Zippy's moving out,
and he's going to be miserable.
So you have
been listening.
Oh.
Oh, say,
dinner was great, Judith.
Thank you for inviting me over.
Of course. You're
Alan's best friend.
Actually, you're
Alan's only friend.
(laughter)
It's funny 'cause it's true.
Oh, honey, uh, could you pass
the potatoes, please?
Oh, I think you've already
had plenty, doughboy. Mm.
(high-pitched):
Ah-ha.
(laughs)
Well, I have to say,
I was shocked when Alan told me
you were getting married again.
Oh, you were shocked?
There was a time
when just the thought
of being touched by his tiny,
clammy hands again
made me throw up
in my mouth a little.
(laughs)
That's all ancient history.
Yeah, if ancient history
was last Thursday.
(Judith and Alan laugh)
(both making kissing sound)
Oh, isn't she great?
No!
She's treating you like crap.
The only people
that get to do that
are people
that do it out of love,
like me and Berta and your mom.
Okay, fine. Me and Berta.
Okay. Me.
It's harmless.
It's just Judith being funny.
Did... did you just twitch?
No, I was just talking
about how funny Judith is.
Okay, look me in the eye
and tell me how much you love
Judith without twitching.
Fine. I love Judith.
There, I said it.
Alan.
You cannot marry this woman.
You deserve better.
I mean, not much better,
but better.
You know who I deserve?
I deserve Lyndsey,
but I can't have her.
She's marrying somebody else,
so I'm taking what I can get.
That's what I do.
I'm a love scavenger.
You're also a house scavenger
and a money scavenger
and an underwear scavenger.
But that doesn't mean
you have to settle.
Yes, it does.
I don't want to die alone.
Maybe you don't realize it,
but there aren't a lot of people
who want to spend the rest
of their lives with me.
Oh, no, I realize it!
Brooke, really, we can get
a hotel for the night.
No, no, no, Dad.
It's fine.
I'll sleep on the couch,
and you guys stay in my room.
Surprise!
Who's this?
Uh, Mom, Dad,
this is, um...
my girlfriend, Jenny.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
I like her.
Oh, hey, I was thinking,
now that Jake's gone...
Mm? - ...I can turn his room
into my man-cave. You know, a
pinball machine, flat-screen
TV, potter's wheel.
No, that's not going to happen.
Oh, you have
plans for it?
No, I'm just not
letting you get
another potter's wheel.
(laughs)
Judith, I have to say,
I cannot take my eyes off
of that ring.
I know. When I first saw it,
I thought it was as fake
as the orgasms
I used to have
when we were married.
(laughs)
That's true.
Very unsatisfactory lover.
(Judith laughs)
JUDITH:
But I mean,
what woman could say no to this?
I can think of one.
Can you think of one, Alan?
Uh, what's going on?
Oh, nothing. I'm just glad
that you were there
to pick up the pieces
after Lyndsey turned down
Alan's proposal.
What?! You proposed
to her before me?
Uh, well, technically,
uh, what I...
Oh, you didn't know?
This is awkward.
Open mouth, remove pie,
insert foot.
So, I'm your second choice?!
No, d-doesn't matter
who was second.
Uh, y-you were the
first to say yes!
I will be the first
to say yes
to seconds of this pie.
You are unbelievable!
No, the important thing is
that we found
each other again.
And you're willing
to settle for me,
and I'm willing
to settle for you.
Settle for this.
Oh! God!
I'm a good friend.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey. How's it going?
Good. Thanks again
for the potter's wheel.
It's the least I could do.
I cost you a wife.
I'm just glad
you, uh, came to your senses.
Yeah, I was just scared.
Didn't want to spend the rest
of my life alone.
Hey, as long as I'm around,
you'll never be alone.
Ah, thanks, buddy.
Oh, shoot. Aah!
Oh, here. Let me help
you out with that.
Oh.
(yells)
Thank God, it was just a dream.
Are you okay, baby?
Did you have a nightmare?
(yells)
(sighs)
I got to get him out of here.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man